arash Sadeghi Amjadi

• arashsadeghiamjadi.me

■ Google Scholar

♥ St. John's, NL

Summary

Highly adaptable and independent programmer with over 8 years of experience in Python, C++, Java, and JavaScript, specializing in software development, AI, and Large Language Models. Proven ability to rapidly prototype and excel in challenging technology projects, demonstrated through experience as a researcher and software developer. Talent in fixing bugs and contributing as a full stack developer, with the capability to contribute to any part of the stack. Possesses effective communication, collaboration, and time management skills, contributing effectively to diverse teams and projects. Independent thinker who excels without constant supervision.

Education

Memorial University of Newfoundland (MUN)

St. John's, NL, Canada

MSc in Computer Science. Focus: BERT Large Language Model for music

Jan 2023

Tabriz, Iran

Middle East Technical University (METU)

Ankara, Turkey

MSc in Mechanical Engineering . Focus: Reinforcement Learning, software development.

Sep 2019 - Sep 2021

BSc in Electrical Engineering. Focus: Software development for Robots

Sep 2015 - Jun 2019

Technical Skills

University of Tabriz

Software: Python, (PyTorch, TensorFlow, NLTK), LLMs (BERT, GPT3, Encoder-Decoder), ReactJS (Material UI), NodeJS, Azure, AWS, Docker, C/C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Git, Jenkins, Unreal Engine, Unity, linux OS,

Skills: Machine/Deep Learning(Computer Vision, Generative Adverserial Networks, Large Language Models, LSTMs), AI, Robotics, Software development, Web development,

Work Experience

MUN St. John's, NL

Teacher Assistance

2023

• Supported game dev (C++), Java OOP, & AI courses as a MUN Teaching Assistant.

GoodAI

Full Stack Software Developer

Prague, Czech Republic

2022-2023

• Developing simulation for drones using 3D simulators like Gazebo and game engines like Unreal Engine 4 and 5 and Unity. Designed and implemented a user-friendly ground station control software using React. is for efficient drone operations management. Implemented object detection and tracking for drone using Deep Learning and Computer Vision.

Czech Technical University (CTU)

Prague, Czech Republic

Software Developer and Researcher

2021-2022

- Led the development of robust Computer Vision and Deep Learning stacks, enabling precise object detection and tracking in complex environments for the Roborovale project.
- Instructed and supported students as a teaching assistant for C/C++ programming.

Projects

Portfolio Website (ReactJS & MaterialUI)

Jan 2023 - Feb 2024

• Built a dynamic and user-friendly portfolio website utilizing ReactJS. Explore more projects at arashsadeghiamjadi.me.

MUN MSc Thesis: Music Generation with GANs and Large Language Models Jan 2023 - Feb 2024

• Developed a website for drum accompanying using GAN AI models and BERT to accompany human players.

Published paper: Web developing for SwarmJS

Jun 2023

• Enabling connections of front-end, ReactJS, to external simulation engines like Python through Web Sockets in the back-end, Flask, enhancing AI capabilities.

METU MSc Thesis: Robot Simulators Development

Sep 2019 - Apr 2021

• Developed dynamic simulators for robots on Webots, ROS, and Python platforms, enhancing exploration capabilities in the KOVAN lab.